http://www.offscreen.be/en/privacy-statement

Skip to main content
Privacy statement | Offscreen
vzw Marcel is the organizer of the Offscreen Film Festival and the activities under the Offscreen label that take place throughout the year, from here on vzw Marcel/Offscreen.vzw Marcel/Offscreen finds privacy important and is careful with personal data following the European privacy laws of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) or AVG 2016/679 of April 27 2016 concerning the protection of individuals regarding the processing and transmission of personal data.This means that vzw Marcel/Offscreen keeps the personal information you provided and uses it only for the purposes described below:With your permission, vzw Marcel/Offscreen uses your email address to send out a newsletter.vzw Marcel/Offscreen doesn't use your information for commercial purposes and will not transfer, rent or sell these, partly or entirely, to any third parties.You have right of access as well as the right to correct or delete any personal data that we have received from you. Underneath this privacy statement are the different ways in which you can contact us.You personally subscribed to the Offscreen newsletter, and these data are contained in the contact information files of the vzw Marcel/Offscreen and are only available through the organization itself. This information is used solely for the promotion of the screenings and activities of the vzw Marcel/Offscreen.If you no longer want to be kept up-to-date with the activities of the vzw Marcel/Offscreen, you can unsubscribe at the bottom of each of our newsletters, or change your preferences.If, after going over this privacy statement, you have any questions or want to contact us, you can do so through the following contact details.Vzw Marcel / OffscreenDe Moranvillestraat 63, 1090 Brusseldirk@offscreen.be0477-792316
Practical infoLocationsPartners + thanksWho is Marcel?ContactNewsletterFacebookTwitterInstagramPrivacy statement
Offscreen photostream
